<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="AD14F0BD-B0D3-425B-B7AF-1FA27601E8EE">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090618" date="2009-06-18 22:17:22 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;So, it&#x2019;s Day 2 of the trip and here I sit on a bed at a Comfort Inn in Crawfordsville, Indiana, aka, the heartland of America.&#xD;&#xD;Since I&#x2019;m starting the travel blog a bit late, I wanted to share my Monday decision to eliminate most of my hair, as you can see in the photo above. As part of our move to the west and the opening of a new chapter of our lives, I wanted to make some other changes. Hair came to mind and since I usually get a shorter cut for the summer, I thought I&#x2019;d go bold and get it cut as short as I used to when I was about 6 years old. I have to say that it feels great. And since I promised Daniel that I would not shave (from June 11) until we got to California, I&#x2019;ve got some facial hair working too.&#xD;&#xD;So far, the trip has been largely uneventful. We&#x2019;ve managed to drive about 350 miles in each of our first two days. We hit a little weather in Wheeling, West Virginia on our first night. We arrived at the hotel (another dog-friendly Comfort Inn) just before the start of a torrential downpour. Fortunately, there were no accompanying tornadoes.&#xD;&#xD;We&#x2019;ve decided to plan our stops one day at a time, identifying a dog-friendly hotel for the next night after stopping for the night. So far, so good.&#xD;&#xD;As for the driving, we&#x2019;re both finding it a bit tiring. I feel the need to stop for a break about once every 90 minutes or so. The days of driving for hours on end are long gone.&#xD;&#xD;Daniel has been a real trooper so far. He&#x2019;s been composing hip-hop lyrics and even using his laptop to do some new freestyles. &#xD;&#xD;The dogs are holding up well too, but I think they&#x2019;re wondering what the heck is going on and &#x201C;when are we going home?&#x201D; Little do they know...&#xD;&#xD;The end of each of the first two days has found us all pretty tired. Daniel and I did have enough energy this evening to throw the football around a bit.&#xD;&#xD;I brought a couple of books to read, but have yet to crack either one. Who knows, maybe tonight&#x2019;s the night.&#xD;&#xD;Tomorrow, we&#x2019;re off to see Lincoln&#x2019;s tomb in Springfield, IL. And then we end the day in Macon, MO. But this time, we&#x2019;re at a Super 8 Motel (the Comfort Inn in Macon does not allow pets...go figure).&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Better late then never</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Wednesday, June 17, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="17_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="326px" height="250px"/>
</content>
