<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="AD14F0BD-B0D3-425B-B7AF-1FA27601E8EE">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090621" date="2009-06-21 19:18:36 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;From Omaha, we made a stop in Lincoln, Nebraska. A friend had told us that that the capitol building was worth a visit. He was right again (this is the same friend who suggested we visit Lincoln&#x2019;s Tomb).&#xD;&#xD;You can catch some more appropriate photos over on the &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="perma://BLPageReference/0F0CDA75-77AE-47AA-A47E-C13BF0116147"&gt;Day 5 page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;. As is often the case with traveling, you hit the bathroom whenever the opportunity arises. The image above is from the Men&#x2019;s Room at the capitol building. It had been so long since I&#x2019;d seen one of these, I could not resist the urge to capture it, and now share it with all of you. One of the inscriptions on the exterior of the building is &#x201C;The salvation of the state is watchfulness in the citizen.&#x201D; Consider this my role in being &#x201C;watchful.&#x201D; Enjoy!&#xD;&#xD;From Lincoln, we headed on to Grand Island, Nebrasks, for a night at the Days Inn. All of the dog-friendly hotels seem to have the same systems in place. What I&#x2019;ve been doing to make our reservations is to go to dogfriendlyhotels.org, find a place in the city where we want to stop, look up the web page of the specific hotel site, and call them directly. By doing this, I get to do 2 things. First, I can verify that they are indeed dog friendly, and second, I get to use my AAA discount, whihc most of these hotels seem to have. The list of chain hotels that seem to predominate the dog-friendly world are Comfort Inn, Days Inn, Quality Inn, and Super 8. At least those are the ones that dogfriendlyhotels.org seems to have identified. They all provide similar length confirmation numbers, and more interestingly, they all seem to have the exact same script for asking for your information. The order has been the same and they all, so far at least, never want to know the city of your home address, they take the street address and then go right to the zip code. That lookup on their reservation system has surely saved them a massive quantity of keystrokes and prevented an enormous quantity of typos.&#xD;&#xD;It is 8am right now on Father&#x2019;s Day and I&#x2019;m laying in bed with my son fast asleep on my right. He&#x2019;s been writing more hip hop lyrics during the trip. In fact, he uses his iPhone to write lyrics in the car (using Notes) and then practices performing them over music that he has in Garageband on his laptop. He does this in the car, not just in the hotel. It&#x2019;s incredible how he&#x2019;s gotten into this. His rhyming skills are improving dramatically. It will be interesting to see where this goes.&#xD;&#xD;We&#x2019;re off to North Platte this morning. It&#x2019;s the home of &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bailey_Yard"&gt;Bailey Yard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;, the largest railyard in the world (according to Wikipedia). Stay tuned...&#xD;&#xD;For those of you wishing to see a Google travel map of our stops, be sure to visit &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=111880012847792298201.00046ccde319ed5cfb6d2&amp;source=embed&amp;ll=43.913723,-94.812012&amp;spn=8.451982,18.061523&amp;z=6"&gt;Cross-Country Adenture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The Watchful Citizen</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Saturday, June 20, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="20_Entry_1_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="333px" height="250px"/>
</content>
