<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="89966811-3039-4C63-AF74-C8C9217F92FA">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090621" date="2009-06-21 23:19:58 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Late yesterday afternoon our driver commented that the house had begun to echo. So it had. Not too long after that the place we had called home for nearly nine years was empty. The chatter from holiday gatherings rang in my head as we walked from room to empty room to ensure that nothing had been left behind. Another step toward our departure had been completed.&#xD;&#xD;Bob and I spent the night in the empty house. I camped on the second floor landing with the dogs because it was the only spot in the house with carpeting. I figured my aging bones could use the cushion. Bob slept on the hardwood floor in our room where the bed had been. We were warm enough in our sleeping bags, but camping out in our own empty house was unsettling; none of us rested well.&#xD; &#xD;Dan had spent the previous day and the night with the Valle family. He loves spending time with his three &#x201C;brothers&#x201D;. Ana Maria was incredibly kind and thoughtful, and did absolutely everything to help Dan feel more comfortable despite the upheaval of moving. Bob and I picked Dan up about 9 this morning. Ana Maria provided us with orange juice, do-nuts and loving company. It was very sad to leave her.&#xD;&#xD;We finally pulled away from the big house on Stout Road at 10:06 am. We managed to drive nearly 100 miles before stopping the first time somewhere along the Pennsylvania turnpike. I took the dogs for a walk in a field which adjoined the rest stop; Dan ate pizza and a cinnamon roll; I fetched a banana from my mobile pantry; Bob did the same. We pushed on.&#xD;After about an hour we stopped at another rest facility. Dan ate baked zitti.&#xD;&#xD;As we drove further west, the farmlands gave way to densely wooded hills. Soon the hills were higher and closer together, and the turnpike threaded in and out of the hills like a long strand of blue yarn.&#xD;&#xD;Around 6 pm we reached Wheeling, West Virginia, our night&#x2019;s destination. Bob checked us in and gathered his and Dan&#x2019;s baggage while I leashed the dogs. We five paraded through the Comfort Inn lobby. I received several admiring glances -- for my dogs. A local man sang out that his Airedale puppy weighs 70 pounds. Oh, my girl (referring to Magic) is 125 pounds I replied over my shoulder. Grunt. Universal dog owner one-upsmanship.&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Empty House, Departure</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, June 16, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="16_Empty_House,_Departure_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="365px" height="263px"/>
</content>
