<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="89966811-3039-4C63-AF74-C8C9217F92FA">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090621" date="2009-06-21 23:19:59 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;At 8:30 it was raining hard, blowing harder yesterday as we ventured out to pack up the cars. I was in a hurry to get my bag into the &#x201C;UpTrunk&#x201D; (cargo box attached to the roof of the Volvo), so I ran out in the rain in my denim skirt, sandals and hooded windbreaker lugging the bag containing my clothes and another with computer gear and documents. I squirreled away the bags in their appointed nooks. By this time the rain had nearly soaked through my windbreaker. The lock on the UpTrunk got stuck as I was closing it so that I could neither lock the box nor remove the key. Frustrated, I stood on the interior door jam of the rear passenger door trying to 1) remove my keys or 2) lock the #*!&amp;% cargo box. Of course, the contents of the car - which I had deemed too valuable to put in the movers&#x2019; truck - was being pelted with rain. I was soaked to the skin, clothes clinging like wet beach towels to my back and legs. I walked away from the car disgusted, dripping wet and leaving the car unlocked and the keys stuck in the UpTrunk.&#xD;&#xD;Bob, with superior hand strength, closed the UpTrunk with annoying ease, and smilingly suggested that it might have been a better idea to move the car to the Comfort Inn&#x2019;s covered entrance before attempting to load it.&#xD;&#xD;We drove in 100 miles bursts, stopping at highway rest stops or fast food joints. Dan continued to eat amazing quantities. No sign of the ugly motion sickness that has dogged (sorry Willie) our previous car trips. &#xD;&#xD;At rest points when the situation permitted I got the dogs out of the car for a comfort stop. They are both very nervous about being left behind - or in any situation where they are not able to see me. Consequently have gone from merely well-behaved to &#x201C;I-think-I&#x2019;ll-get-them-a-TV-job&#x201D;.&#xD;&#xD;Bob thoroughly enjoys rubbing his palms over his new hairdo. He says it is cool and comfy. I suppose it must be, but so far imitation has not crossed my mind.&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Travel Day 2, Wheeling to Crawfordsville</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thursday, June 18, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="18_Travel_Day_2,_Wheeling_to_Crawfordsville_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="333px" height="250px"/>
</content>
