<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="89966811-3039-4C63-AF74-C8C9217F92FA">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090621" date="2009-06-21 23:20:00 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;We were just so worn out last night that we didn&#x2019;t have it in us to take in the tourist spots of Hannibal. I wouldn&#x2019;t hear of moving on without at least gawking at the Mississippi, so this morning we drove the three or so miles back into town.&#xD;&#xD;Hannibal is a little place, with an old-fashioned main street. There are numerous shop signs displaying the name &#x201C;Mark&#x201D; or &#x201C;Twain&#x201D; or &#x201C;Tom&#x201D;. There&#x2019;s a bronze statue of Tom Sawyer and Huck, another of Samuel Clemens, and a big billboard advertising admissions to Tom and Becky&#x2019;s cave. Downtown there&#x2019;s a Mark Train Museum, which we did not pay the 9 (or was it 14?) dollars a head to enter, and Mark Twain&#x2019;s Boyhood Home. We didn&#x2019;t locate Twain&#x2019;s home even though it would have been easy enough to do. The heat must have got to us.&#xD;&#xD;Seems that the town is not typically awash in tourists, as the place is off the beaten track. I take the locals&#x2019; very congenial attitude toward tourists as evidence for this supposition. We were given accurate directions politely, and the good old boys sitting on a park bench shot a good-natured question or two about Magic. &#x201C;Ya gotta black bear there, Ma&#x2019;am?&#x201D; &#x201C;No, she&#x2019;s a beast of burden&#x201D;. Smiles and nods.&#xD;&#xD;Bob, the pups and I strolled down to the river park, where there&#x2019;s some simple landscaping, a fountain and a bronze of Samuel Clemens as a young river pilot. From the park you can look upriver to the steel highway bridge and beyond to the distant bend where muddy water disappears. Near where the bridge joins the shore, a substantial wooded bluff overlooks the river. Close to the park, moored at a small wharf is The Mark Twain Riverboat. A schedule boasts four river tours daily. Downstream, beyond the wharf, the Mississippi&#x2019;s muddy water seems to widen.&#xD;&#xD;We drove into Omaha during evening rush hour. Bob was leading the way and we got separated in the heavy traffic. I thought I had my eye on his car up ahead but at a fork in the highway, he traveled left, I turned right. Oops. Unfortunately, at that point I didn&#x2019;t know the precise location of the hotel... After a stop to get directions from locals, and a phone conversation with Bob (how did we cope before cell phones?) I got back on the road and finally arrived at the hotel just a few minutes behind the boys.&#xD;&#xD;Room service last night at our hotel. Bob enjoyed a steak and a couple of beers, Dan lasagna, the dogs split a plain burger and I had a salad. Then came the hard part: trying to sleep. Our neighbors were boisterous, the air conditioning wasn&#x2019;t powerful enough to deal with the high humidity. College baseball world series was going on with apparently lots of the players staying at our hotel. (No ice in the ice machine this morning; the kids emptied it filling their coolers.) I slept very little; Bob, Dan and dogs were all good to go this morning.&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Travel Day 4, Hannibal, Lost on the highway, Sleepless in Omaha</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, June 19, 2009&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="19_Travel_Day_4,_Hannibal_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="333px" height="250px"/>
</content>
