<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="89966811-3039-4C63-AF74-C8C9217F92FA">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090624" date="2009-06-24 17:57:05 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Western landscapes really tug at my heart. I love the subtle colors of the high prairie scrub brush, the lonesome gnarled trees, powdery dry creek beds, such a big open sky, then in the distance those purple blue mountains. I get a grin on my face and tears in my eyes. Can&#x2019;t help it, there&#x2019;s just something about the spare beauty of the west that makes me crazy.&#xD;&#xD;Back to the trip. Our Days Inn room in Rock Springs had been stuffy, what with three weary travelers and two hot dogs holed up in a room with no window and an ancient window cooler. None of us really rested all that well. We were up and out to get breakfast a little earlier than usual because of it. It was wonderful to take in some early sunshine and the cool dry chill of the morning on the brief walk to eat.&#xD;&#xD;We pulled out of our hotel around 8:20. We took the drive easy, as in the back of my mind at least, was the &#x201C;check engine&#x201D; dash warning, and we needed to cross more or less 150 miles of dry country with minimal services before we reached Salt Lake City and the nearest Volvo repair shop.&#xD;&#xD;Our drive was lovely, clear hard light grazing the landscape, throwing even tiny cracks and bumps into high relief. From behind my steering wheel, the soil seemed by turns chalky, beige, caramel or dusty red. For a short spell some green earth, in fuzzy striations, appeared on the south side of the highway. In a few miles it disappeared, although I continued to look for related traces of green, or a road sign announcing which mineral had so painted the hot landscape. Didn&#x2019;t see either. For me not knowing precisely what or why only enhances the landscape, as the unanswered questions increase the sense of wonder and mystery. Not having the answers, or not even knowing which questions to ask, can push an experience from the mind to the heart. That&#x2019;s where I think this landscape belongs -- in the heart. &#xD;&#xD;Later in the morning the sky turned a hot, intense blue. At the highway&#x2019;s vanishing point a cluster of strange silvery shapes appeared. Oz? A kingdom of crystal skyscrapers? These were not mountains, they looked more like the sails of a mammoth schooner. After what seemed like an eternity of guessing, the meaning of the strange forms became apparent. Wind turbines.&#xD;&#xD;They had been painted white, but in the crisp air and brilliant sunshine they reflected both the sky and the surrounding land. Because the massive blades twirled the reflected colors switched in rapid fire. My eyes and brain can&#x2019;t process the color shift fast enough; the color switches and after-imaging were interpreted as silver. Very cool.&#xD;&#xD;Details on our car repair hiatus in Salt Lake City. The &#x201C;check engine&#x201D; was a warning that my car wasn&#x2019;t firing all cylinders. (Put aside childish jokes for the moment, please.) Bob became worried about his brakes and had them repaired. Anyway, these mechanical problems  devoured several hours of the afternoon. After my car was repaired, I took the dogs on a motor tour of Salt Lake City. We drove up to Capitol Hill, Temple Square, Salt Palace. &#xD;&#xD;Back on the highway. As you drive along I-80 west with Salt Lake City at your back, you almost immediately come upon the huge lake for which the city is named. White crystalline mounds and powdery drifts strewn about the shore and the shallows remind you that this water really is saturated with minerals; salt lake is not some fanciful misnomer.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Day, 8 Red Desert, Wind Power, Blue Haze</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, June 23, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="23_Day,_8_Red_Desert,_Wind_Power,_Blue_Haze_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="333px" height="250px"/>
</content>
