<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="89966811-3039-4C63-AF74-C8C9217F92FA">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20090630" date="2009-06-30 00:17:09 -0400"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;We are still pretty worn out from our drive, but feeling more bright-eyed every day.&#xD;&#xD;When we first arrived the dogs were absolutely confused. Was this just another over-night stop? Whenever I would get my car keys and head for the Volvo, Willie and Magic would start to jump and collide nervously. You&#x2019;re not leaving us behind, are you? @#@^??&gt;(*&amp;!!! (That&#x2019;s dog swearing.) After a couple of days here they are beginning to relax.&#xD;&#xD;Our first task upon arrival was to head to Pier One and purchase chairs. Now we all have a place to sit. Luxury! The kitchen has a small built-in desk which we all use in turn for computer work. Since all the appliances, including washer and dryer, are built-in we have all the conveniences. While sleeping on the wood floor in sleeping bags isn&#x2019;t deluxe, it has made for some great jokes and some memorable moments. Movers arrive on Wednesday.&#xD;&#xD;Today Comcast arrived and hooked up our internet and television services. We are all very happy about this. Bob gets to watch Wimbledon and catch up on correspondence on his laptop instead of his phone. Dan found his way back into iTunes immediately, and I set out to finish up the trip blog.&#xD;&#xD;Dan is restless. He makes lots of calls to kids in NJ and spends lots of time on iChat. He&#x2019;s feeling disjointed and probably a bit depressed, but once we become involved in neighborhood or school activities, his malaise will pass. &#xD;&#xD;This morning, with surprising willingness, Dan began reading one of the two novels he must have finished by the time school begins on August 18. Steinbeck&#x2019;s &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Travels with Charlie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;, could not be more appropriate for a young man who just completed a cross-country trip in the company of two dogs. Willie even resembles a Standard Poodle!&#xD;&#xD;The pool has been grand fun. Every afternoon so far we&#x2019;ve headed for the pool. Our great entertainment is trying to coax Willie and Magic into the pool. Magic has gone in as far as her belly, then beat a hasty retreat. Willie has dipped one paw with great trepidation, then joined Magic in the shade.&#xD;&#xD;We&#x2019;re grateful to friends and family who have been sending encouraging messages. Thank you!! Dan is thrilled whenever he hears from a pal from New Jersey. Please continue to keep him company!&#xD;&#xD;We wish you all a wonderful summer, with luck you will also enjoy at least one terrific adventure. &#xD;&#xD;Take good care and keep in touch.&#xD;&#xD;Sandra&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Home Sweet Home</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Monday, June 29, 2009&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="29_Home_Sweet_Home_files/shapeimage_2.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="333px" height="250px"/>
</content>
