<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Bob's Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog</link>
    <description>Right attcha: Random thoughts and ideas on various subjects.</description>
    <item>
      <title>The Watchful Citizen</title>
      <link>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/20_Entry_1.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">feef1627-c88c-4f6f-91b0-306ff5baaefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 08:44:17 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>From Omaha, we made a stop in Lincoln, Nebraska. A friend had told us that that the capitol building was worth a visit. He was right again (this is the same friend who suggested we visit Lincoln&#x2019;s Tomb).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You can catch some more appropriate photos over on the &lt;a href="../Day_5.html"&gt;Day 5 page&lt;/a&gt;. As is often the case with traveling, you hit the bathroom whenever the opportunity arises. The image above is from the Men&#x2019;s Room at the capitol building. It had been so long since I&#x2019;d seen one of these, I could not resist the urge to capture it, and now share it with all of you. One of the inscriptions on the exterior of the building is &#x201C;The salvation of the state is watchfulness in the citizen.&#x201D; Consider this my role in being &#x201C;watchful.&#x201D; Enjoy!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;From Lincoln, we headed on to Grand Island, Nebrasks, for a night at the Days Inn. All of the dog-friendly hotels seem to have the same systems in place. What I&#x2019;ve been doing to make our reservations is to go to dogfriendlyhotels.org, find a place in the city where we want to stop, look up the web page of the specific hotel site, and call them directly. By doing this, I get to do 2 things. First, I can verify that they are indeed dog friendly, and second, I get to use my AAA discount, whihc most of these hotels seem to have. The list of chain hotels that seem to predominate the dog-friendly world are Comfort Inn, Days Inn, Quality Inn, and Super 8. At least those are the ones that dogfriendlyhotels.org seems to have identified. They all provide similar length confirmation numbers, and more interestingly, they all seem to have the exact same script for asking for your information. The order has been the same and they all, so far at least, never want to know the city of your home address, they take the street address and then go right to the zip code. That lookup on their reservation system has surely saved them a massive quantity of keystrokes and prevented an enormous quantity of typos.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is 8am right now on Father&#x2019;s Day and I&#x2019;m laying in bed with my son fast asleep on my right. He&#x2019;s been writing more hip hop lyrics during the trip. In fact, he uses his iPhone to write lyrics in the car (using Notes) and then practices performing them over music that he has in Garageband on his laptop. He does this in the car, not just in the hotel. It&#x2019;s incredible how he&#x2019;s gotten into this. His rhyming skills are improving dramatically. It will be interesting to see where this goes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We&#x2019;re off to North Platte this morning. It&#x2019;s the home of &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bailey_Yard"&gt;Bailey Yard&lt;/a&gt;, the largest railyard in the world (according to Wikipedia). Stay tuned...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For those of you wishing to see a Google travel map of our stops, be sure to visit &lt;a href="http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;msa=0&amp;msid=111880012847792298201.00046ccde319ed5cfb6d2&amp;source=embed&amp;ll=43.913723,-94.812012&amp;spn=8.451982,18.061523&amp;z=6"&gt;Cross-Country Adenture&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object007.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/20_Entry_1.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sawyer I am not</title>
      <link>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/19_Tom_Sawyer_I_am_not.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0feea32-a20f-41bc-a75a-f40e46d73adf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 08:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Friday found us stopping in Hannibal, Missouri, boyhood home of Mark Twain. The Quality Inn was a fine stop. The room was large and cold (it had been a very hot day, so the blast of air-conditioned cold was a welcomed relief).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since Daniel is not a great traveler and prefers not to sight-see, our time in historic downtown Hannibal was brief. It&#x2019;s a quaint little town, filled with antique shops and it sita at the edge of the Mississippi River.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The photo above is a dogs-eye view of a beautiful building on Main Street.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our next stop is set for Omaha, Nebraska, home of Warren Buffet (though, I doubt we&#x2019;ll spot him).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So far, we&#x2019;re all holding up well. I&#x2019;m glad we decided to do about 300 miles a day. That&#x2019;s long enough with the 2 cars and the dog stops.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object002.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/19_Tom_Sawyer_I_am_not.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois, land of Lincoln</title>
      <link>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/18_i_dont_know_yet.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30e6e133-6b2f-4b70-b5f3-238e87596a4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 22:22:49 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>Today, we got of to a late start from Crawfordsville, Indiana. The weather outlook was very severe, at least according to the weather channel. We sat tight and waited until around 11am to check out and get on the road. I had discovered the National Weather Service web site (far more credible than weatherchannel.com). From the NWS site, it appeared that the worst was headed south in a hurry and we would be driving into clear skies. Thankfully, that&#x2019;s exactly what happened. The day was great...a bit hot by mid-day...but nice nonetheless.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We drove to Springfield, IL to visit Lincoln&#x2019;s Tomb, a site recommended by by a friend. He was right. The site is both impressive and inspiring. Regrettably, our son had absolutely no interest in seeing it, so he waited in the car.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Due to the weather and the late start, we had managed to book 3 hotels over the course of the day. We had originally planned to make it as far as Macon, OH, which would have made it a 300+ mile day (day 1 and 2 were each about 350 miles). We cancelled the Macon hotel and decided to be cautious and shoot for Decatur, IL. Once we hit the clear skies, we shot easily past Decatur and managed to book a place in Hannibal, Mo, the boyhood home of Mark Twain. We arrived at the hotel at around 5pm and it was quite hot outside; probably around 90 degrees. The room was an icebox and it felt great. It&#x2019;s also large and the building appears to be either new or freshly remodeled. The wifi is great too. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tomorrow, we&#x2019;ll spend some time in historic downtown Hannibal and check out the Mark Twain&#x2019;ings of it all. Then we plan to head to St. Joseph, MO. At that point, the next day, we&#x2019;ll turn north and head to Lincoln, NE.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;That&#x2019;s it for now...</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object050.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/18_i_dont_know_yet.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better late then never</title>
      <link>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/17.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e3c62a4-fedb-4ab1-babd-dc046b6df7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 21:33:25 -0400</pubDate>
      <description>So, it&#x2019;s Day 2 of the trip and here I sit on a bed at a Comfort Inn in Crawfordsville, Indiana, aka, the heartland of America.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Since I&#x2019;m starting the travel blog a bit late, I wanted to share my Monday decision to eliminate most of my hair, as you can see in the photo above. As part of our move to the west and the opening of a new chapter of our lives, I wanted to make some other changes. Hair came to mind and since I usually get a shorter cut for the summer, I thought I&#x2019;d go bold and get it cut as short as I used to when I was about 6 years old. I have to say that it feels great. And since I promised Daniel that I would not shave (from June 11) until we got to California, I&#x2019;ve got some facial hair working too.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So far, the trip has been largely uneventful. We&#x2019;ve managed to drive about 350 miles in each of our first two days. We hit a little weather in Wheeling, West Virginia on our first night. We arrived at the hotel (another dog-friendly Comfort Inn) just before the start of a torrential downpour. Fortunately, there were no accompanying tornadoes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We&#x2019;ve decided to plan our stops one day at a time, identifying a dog-friendly hotel for the next night after stopping for the night. So far, so good.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As for the driving, we&#x2019;re both finding it a bit tiring. I feel the need to stop for a break about once every 90 minutes or so. The days of driving for hours on end are long gone.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Daniel has been a real trooper so far. He&#x2019;s been composing hip-hop lyrics and even using his laptop to do some new freestyles. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The dogs are holding up well too, but I think they&#x2019;re wondering what the heck is going on and &#x201C;when are we going home?&#x201D; Little do they know...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The end of each of the first two days has found us all pretty tired. Daniel and I did have enough energy this evening to throw the football around a bit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I brought a couple of books to read, but have yet to crack either one. Who knows, maybe tonight&#x2019;s the night.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Tomorrow, we&#x2019;re off to see Lincoln&#x2019;s tomb in Springfield, IL. And then we end the day in Macon, MO. But this time, we&#x2019;re at a Super 8 Motel (the Comfort Inn in Macon does not allow pets...go figure).</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object007_1.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment link="http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog/Entries/2009/6/17.html#comment_layer" count="0" enabled="0"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, MMMM d, yyyy</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://www.allfeetondeck.com/Return_of_the_Natives/Bobs_Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
